[BLANK_AUDIO]
It's always odd and it fakes, then it wants to break.
We're done the best ten hours late.
Snap your fingers, oops, you're fluent.
Now your stuff look blue and we're with everyone.
Screw it twice, waffle to the cost of bad advice.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Take one line, crash the site.
Double deal through half the night.
Draw the tag off, snow return.
Now your wallet gets a burn.
Cut the wire you should have cut.
Full house smells like a rut.
You bleed blunts and nuke the vibe.
Now you owe beers to the hope tries.
Always are a fix, then it wants to break.
The sandals left, now you're all day.
Snap the scissors, light bulb joins.
Hope you like patching, made a poke hole.
Is it once, wreck it fast.
Good luck cleaning up your past.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> Friend of mine over to me on one way.
He had a door to fall, but he had a three hour first boot.
[BLANK_AUDIO]